我们带了晚餐
We brought dinner.
没事
It's okay.
你们进来吧
Come on in, guys.
进行下一步之前
Before we take this any further,
我需要你们上交武器
I need you all to turn over your weapons.
要留下来 就得上交
Stay, you hand them over.
我们还不确定想不想留下来
We don't know if we want to stay.
没事的 尼古拉斯
It's fine, Nicholas.
我们要用武器早就用了
If we were gonna use them, we would have started already.
让他们先跟迪安娜谈谈
Let them talk to Deanna first.
迪安娜是谁
Who's Deanna?
她能告诉你们这地方的一切情况
She knows everything you'd want to know about this place.
瑞克 你先开始吧
Rick, why don't you start?
萨沙
Sasha.
还好我们来了
It's a good thing we're here.
《行尸走肉》
你好
Hello.
我是迪安娜·门罗
I'm Deanna Monroe.
瑞克·格兰姆斯
Rick Grimes.
- 你介意我拍下来吗 - 什么
- You mind if I film this? - What?
你介意我拍下我们的聊天吗
Do you mind if I film our talk?
拍吧
Go ahead.
为什么要拍
Why film this?
我们这里讲求透明
We're about transparency here.
请坐
Please.
你在外面闯荡多久了
How long have you been out there?
从灾变开始
Since the beginning.
你们怎么找到彼此的
How did you all find each other?
之前就认识吗 还是…
Did you know each other before or...?
我们之前不认识
We didn't know each other before.
我曾是国会议员
I was a congressperson.
俄亥俄州 第15选区
Ohio, 15th district.
你呢
You?
我觉得这不重要
I don't think it matters anymore.
我知道这很重要
Oh, I know it does.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
"可持续生活的开始"
This is the start of sustainability.
这是我们找到的小册子上说的
That's what the brochures we found say.
这是个规划社区
This was a planned community
拥有太阳能独立电网 蓄水池
with its own solar grid, cisterns,
生态性污水过滤系统
eco-based sewage filtration.
起价是八十万出头
Starting in the low 800,000s...
简直是天价
...if there is such a thing.
但全卖光了
And they sold them all.
你怎么来到这里的
How did you end up here?
我和家人想回到俄亥俄州
Well, my family and I were trying to get back to Ohio
我好帮助我的选区应对危机
so I could help my district manage the crisis.
然而
And...
军队在小路上拦住了我们
...the army stopped us on a back road
指引我们来到这里
and directed us here.
他们本该稍后过来的
They were supposed to come later.
他们没来
They didn't.
但是这里有物资
But there were supplies here
我们尽力利用了
and we made the best of it.
你建起了围墙吗
You put up the wall?
附近有一家大型商场在施工
Well, there was this huge shopping mall being built nearby.
我丈夫雷吉是建筑学教授
And my husband Reg is a professor of architecture.
他以前的身份相当重要
And who he was mattered quite a bit.
他跟我们的儿子们竖起了第一块板子
He got the first plates up with our sons.
几周过后 更多人来了
And after a few weeks, more people arrived
我们有了帮手
and we had help.
我们建立了社区
We had a community.
一直以来你们都躲在这些墙后面吗
You've been behind these walls this entire time?
我们需要在外面闯荡过的人
We need people who have lived out there.
你的团队是我们长久以来
Your group is the first we've even considered
唯一考虑过接纳的队伍
taking in for a long time.
你们应该关上门
You should keep your gates closed.
为什么
Why?
因为现在生存是最重要的
Because it's all about survival now.
不择手段
At any cost.
外面的人虎视眈眈
People out there are always looking for an angle.
伺机利用你的弱点
Looking to play on your weakness.
他们只在乎
They measure you
你有什么价值
by what they can take from you.
怎么利用你生存
By how they can use you to live.
所以如今带人来这种地方…
So bringing people into a place like this now...
你是说我不该带你们来吗
Are you telling me not to bring your people in?
你已经开始为这个地方着想了吗
Are you already looking after this place?
亚伦说我可以信任你
Aaron says I can trust you.
亚伦不了解我
Aaron doesn't know me.
我杀过人
I've killed people.
数都数不清
I don't even know how many by now.
但是我知道为什么他们都死了
But I know why they're all dead.
只有他们死了 我的家人
They're dead so my family,
和外面那些人才能活下去
all those people out there, can be alive.
我也才能为了他们活下去
So I could be alive for them.
听得我都想成为你的家人了
Sounds like I'd want to be part of your family.
瑞克
Rick,
北弗吉尼亚州疏散得非常成功
northern Virginia was effectively evacuated.
数百万的民众都离开了
Millions of people gone.
很长一段时间以来 这里几乎没有人了
For a long time, there's hardly been anyone here,
活人死人都没有 但是…
living or dead, but still...
我们还是损失了一些人
we have lost people.
而且…
And...
我还干过一些事
I've done things.
你干了什么
What have you done?
我流放了三个不适合这里的人
I exiled three men who didn't work out.
我们都知道那和杀了他们没有差别
And we both know that's as good as killing them.
你想从我们这里得到什么
What do you want from us?
这些家庭…
These families...
这些家庭应该在安全的环境中
these families should be able to raise their children
抚养自己的孩子
in a safe environment.
你的儿子 你的女儿
Your son, your daughter,
他们应该有个地方成长
should have a place to grow up.
我想要什么
What do I want?
我想要你帮我们生存下去
I want you to help us survive.
我知道你可以帮我们做到
I know you can help us do that.
怎么帮
How?
我很会看人
I am exceptionally good at reading people.
要不是我连任了
If I didn't win reelection,
我本来要去当职业扑克牌玩家的
I was gonna be a professional poker player.
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
瑞克
Rick...
现在是下午3点37分
It's 3:37 p.m.
你有顾虑
You're skeptical.
这是你的权利
You have a right to be.
但现在是时候做决定了
But it's time to decide
假如你是做决定的人
if you're the one who's doing the deciding.
我当过县警
I was a sheriff.
是啊 我就知道是这类职业
Yeah, I knew it was something like that.
这些仍然是你们的枪
They're still your guns.
你们外出时可以随时领走
You can check them out whenever you go beyond the wall.
但是在里面时 由我们保管
But inside here, we store them for safety.
应该多带一个箱子来的
Should have brought another bin.
- 两栋都是我们的吗 - 随你处置
- Both of 'em? - At your disposal.
换我就选那一栋
I'd call dibs on that one.
外观更吸引人
It's got more curb appeal.
听着 我知道你们仍在观察我们
Listen, I know you're still feeling us out,
但我很高兴你们来了
but I'm glad you came.
总之 迪安娜叫大家给你们一点空间
Anyway, Deanna's asked everyone to give you your space
所以他们不会一窝蜂跑来找你
so they aren't all coming at you at once.
你们慢慢来 四处走走
Take your time. Explore.
有任何需要的话 给我打电话
You need anything, you call me.
我没有…我们没有电话
I don't... we don't have phones.
我的意思是…再走四栋就是我家
I... I meant... I'm four houses down.
- 谢谢 - 那…
- Thank you. - So...
你好 我是食品室的
Hey. I work in the pantry.
迪安娜叫我把这些给你和你的朋友们
Deanna asked me to bring these over for you and your friends.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们正在洗漱
We're just cleaning up.
看出来了
I can see that.
你下巴上还沾着剃须膏
You still have some shaving cream on your chin.
我是杰茜
I'm Jessie.
瑞克
Rick.
知道吗 我以前是发型师
You know, I used to be a stylist.
还有别的十二份工作
And 12 other things.
如果你愿意 我可以帮你剪头
I could give you a cut if you want.
你都不认识我
You don't even know me.
我能照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
我有两个儿子 罗恩和山姆
I have two boys, Ron and Sam.
罗恩是大儿子 跟你儿子差不多大
Ron's my oldest boy. He's about your son's age.
我可以介绍他们认识
I could introduce them.
- 如果你和夫人没意见的话 - 只剩我了
- If that's okay with you and... - It's just me.
好啊 那很好
No, that'd be...that'd be great.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
电 淋浴
Electricity, showers,
理发
haircuts...
没想到我还能见到这些
I never thought I'd see those again.
拜托
Come on.
什么情况下都得理发
Haircuts were never going away.
如果你还不适应 没有关系
It's okay if you're not okay with this yet.
好多了
That's better.
你可以坐下 达里尔
You're welcome to sit, Daryl.
我不咬人
I won't bite.
没事 这样很好
Yeah, I'm all right.
达里尔 你想不想留下
Daryl, do you want to be here?
那个男孩和婴儿
The boy and the baby,
他们应该有个家
they deserve a roof.
应该吧
I guess.
你可以去看看 快点回来
You can look. Just be quick.
好
Okay.
这些简直是豪宅
These are like mansions.
他们就这么白送给我们了
Mm-hmm. And they're just giving them away.
走吗
You coming?
走 马上
Yeah, in a sec.
房子离得都很近 但是…
They're right next to each other, but...
他们收了我们的武器 现在又把我们分开
They took our weapons and now they're splitting us up.
- 是啊 - 是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
今晚我们住在一起
We'll all be staying in the same house tonight.
(斗狼)
我在里面待了多久
How long was I in there for?
二十分钟
20 minutes.
天啊 我刷牙根本停不下来
God, I could not stop brushing.
我从来没有
I've never...
见过你脸这样
I've never seen your face like that.
我也这么觉得 刮前刮后都是
That's what I felt before and after.
听着
Look...
我知道我们为什么谨慎
I get why we're playing it safe.
我们应该这样
We should.
我只是
I just...
对这地方感觉很好
I have a good feeling about this place.
但愿你是对的
Well, I hope you're right.
是啊 但愿
Yeah, me, too.
瑞克 我
Rick, I...
没想到你脸这么俊
I didn't know what was under there.
听着 我不是有意打扰
Listen, I don't mean to interrupt.
我只是顺道来看看你们安顿得怎么样
I just wanted to stop by and see how you were all settling.
天啊
Oh, my.
住在一起
Staying together.
聪明
Smart.
没人说不能住一起
No one said we couldn't.
你说过你们是一家人 你自己说的
You said you're a family. That's what you said.
难以置信 你们这些
Absolutely amazing to me how people
背景迥异 毫无共性的人
with completely different backgrounds
竟能组成大家庭
and nothing in common can become that.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
我听说你会给人分配工作
Everybody said you gave them jobs.
是啊
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
是这里的规矩
Part of this place.
看来共产主义者最终还是赢了
Looks like the communists won after all.
你没有给我分配工作
Well, you didn't give me one.
我分配好了
I have.
只是还没告诉你
I just haven't told you yet.
米琼恩我也没告诉呢
Same with Michonne.
萨沙的工作我就快想好了
I'm closing in on something for Sasha.
迪克森先生适合什么工作我还在考虑
And I'm just trying to figure Mr. Dixon out,
但我会想出来的
but I will.
挺精神的
You look good.
如果一切真如你所说
If this is how you're saying it is...
那我们想留下来
then this is what we wanted.
我们准备好了
We're ready for this.
你们所有人吗
All of you?
所有人
All of us.
他们说四处走走
They said explore.
我们走吧
Let's explore.
不 我就待这儿
Nah, I'll stay.
好吧
All right.
洛莉和我
Lori and me,
我们曾经开车路过这样的社区
we used to drive through neighborhoods like this.
想着"总有一天…"
Thinking, "One day..."
现在我们住上了
Well, here we are.
我们去去就回
We'll be back.
快跟上 快点
Come on. Come on.
瑞克 你没事吧
Rick, you okay?
你看见卡尔和朱迪思了吗
Did Carl and Judith walk by?
我们在外面 他们走在我前头
We were out and they were ahead of me.
别担心 我知道他们在哪
It's okay. I think I know where they are.
那是娜塔莉和鲍勃·米勒
That's Natalie and Bob Miller.
他们曾有五个孩子和十二个孙子孙女
They had five kids and 12 grandkids.
这里的人好久没见过婴儿了
It's been a long time since anyone around here has seen a baby.
她的脸蛋肯定会被捏红的
She's gonna have to put up with some pinched cheeks.
谢了 我只是
Thanks. I just, um...
没关系 我明白
It's okay. I get it.
抱歉我弄坏了那个什么东西
Look, I'm sorry I broke whatever that was I broke.
是我和孩子们一起在做的雕像
It's a sculpture I'm making with the boys.
是个猫头鹰
It's an owl.
完成后就是猫头鹰了
I mean, it will be.
眼睛我怎么都雕不好
I just can't get the eyes right.
是啊 眼睛
Right, the eyes.
你都没仔细看它
You didn't even get a good look at it.
我当时忙着发疯呢
I was in the middle of losing my mind.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
瑞克
Hey, Rick.
卡尔现在过来可以吗
Would it be okay if Carl came over now?
罗恩想见见他
Ron really wants to meet him.
放学后我们基本都在这里
We're almost always here after school,
你可以随时来
so you can come by any time.
你们还上学吗
You go to school?
在一个车库里
It's in a garage.
上午是小孩子去上课
Little kids go in the morning
我们是下午去
and then it's us in the afternoon.
你可能也会去 对吧
Probably you, too, right?
可能吧
Probably.
各位 这是卡尔
Guys, this is Carl.
卡尔 这是米奇和伊妮德
Carl, this is Mikey and Enid.
伊妮德也是外来的人
Enid's from outside, too.
她是八个月前到的
She just came eight months ago.
对了
Oh, um...
这是你们的吗
is this yours?
抱歉
Sorry.
我们不知道那栋房子分你们了
We didn't know you guys got that house.
我们只是在那里玩玩 听听音乐
We mostly just hang out there and listen to music.
是伊妮德的
That's Enid's.
你想打游戏吗
Want to play some video games?
米奇家还有个台球桌
Or Mikey's house has a pool table,
但是他爸爸不让别人玩
but his dad's kind of strict about it.
没关系 他工作去了
It's okay. He's at work.
抱歉 我们有点吓到你了
Sorry, I guess we come on kind of strong.
我们随便玩玩就行
We can just hang out.
如果你不想说话 可以不说
You don't even have to talk if you don't wanna.
是啊 伊妮德三周后才开始说话
Yeah, took Enid three weeks to say something.
快振作起来 小伙子
Pull it together, sport.
我们
Let's, um...
我们玩电子游戏吧
let's play some video games.
好啊
Cool, yeah.
这就是我妈想要我们住的地方
This is the kind of place my mom wanted for us.
很遗憾你失去了她
I'm sorry you lost her.
我不仅仅是失去了她
I didn't just lose her.
我还亲手杀了她
I killed her.
必须是我来动手
It had to be me.
罗恩的房子怎么样
How was Ron's house?
你觉得这个地方怎么样
What do you think of this place?
我觉得这个地方看起来
Well, I think it seems...
很不错
nice.
没错
Yeah.
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
我喜欢这里的人
I like the people.
但是他们很弱
But they're weak.
我不想让我们也变弱
And I don't want us to get weak, too.
迪安娜还没给我安排工作
Deanna hasn't given me a job yet.
你想要工作吗
You want one?
是的
Yeah.
你想吗
Do you?
那就是签字了
That's signing the papers.
就代表正式同意了 就是这么回事
That's saying yes, this is how it is.
你害怕这样做吗
You afraid to do that?
你不害怕吗
Aren't you?
不
No.
那为什么我俩都醒了
So then why are we both awake?
我要出去走走
I'm gonna take a walk.
你是瑞克
You're Rick.
是的
Yeah.
我妻子帮你剪了头发
My wife cut your hair.
没错
Yeah.
欢迎来到亚历山大
Welcome to Alexandria.
我洗衣服 打理花园
I did laundry, gardened, um...
当爱德回到家时
always had dinner on the table for Ed
总为他备好饭菜
when he came home. Um...
我每天都在想念那个笨笨的好男人
I miss that stupid, wonderful man every day.
我无法对团队做出什么贡献
You know, I really didn't have much to offer this group,
所以我就成为了他们的保姆
so I think I just sort of became their den mother.
他们人也很好 一直保护着我
And they've been nice enough to protect me.
你认为自己适合做什么
Where do you think you'll fit in?
我希望可以参与到社区活动中去
Well, I'd like to be involved in the community.
你们有没有类似青年联盟的组织
Do you have anything like a Junior League?
我很善于与人打交道
I'm a real people person.
该打卡上班做炖菜咯
Time to punch the clock and make the casseroles.
什么
What?
给老人家做晚餐
Make dinner for the older people...
还有需要休息一下的主妇和不能做饭的人
moms who need a break, people who can't cook.
这样可以结识很多邻居
Get to meet a lot of the neighbors that way.
好吧
All right.
你洗澡了吗
Have you taken a shower yet?
快去洗吧 我会洗你那件背心
Take a shower. I'm gonna wash that vest.
大家都要保持体面 你也不例外
We need to keep up appearances, even you.
我以前就这样 何必现在改
Hey, I ain't starting now.
我会趁你睡觉时用水管冲你
I'm gonna hose you down in your sleep.
你看起来真扯
You look ridiculous.
我们必须留下来
We need to make this work.
为什么
Why?
因为
'Cause...
我们在外面待得太久了
we were almost out there too long.
格伦 塔拉 诺亚
Glenn, Tara, Noah?
幸会 我是艾登
Nice to meet you. I'm Aiden.
这位是把守大门的尼古拉斯 你们见过的
You met Nicholas pulling gate duty.
你是迪安娜的儿子吗
You're Deanna's son?
是的 我听说你有寻找补给的经验
That's right. I hear you got experience making supply runs.
我看过你们的食品室 你们似乎做得挺好
I saw your pantry. You guys seem to do pretty well.
是啊 我以前在大学储备军官团训练过
Yeah, well, had some training before this. ROTC.
都快升中尉了 结果灾变了
Was nearing lieutenant when this shit blew in.
- 我爸也是储备军官 - 他没活下来吗
- My dad did ROTC. - He didn't make it?
没有
Nah.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我最近老是说这话
I'm sorry a lot these days.
来吧 我给你们指点一下窍门
Come on, I'll show you the ropes.
我们今天要去找补给吗
We're doing a run today?
只是演习
Just a dry run.
带你们看看外面的地形 看看你们的水平
Show you the terrain outside the walls, see how you do.
摸摸你们有没有种 懂吗
Weigh each other's sack a little, you know?
不懂 没摸过 但是行啊
No, I don't, but cool.
- 那武器呢 - 对了
- What about weapons? - Oh, yeah.
今天我们带了些不错的小玩意儿出来
We pulled out some sweet-ass biscuits for today.
准备好
Get ready.
爸
Dad.
我们一直在逐步扩大搜索范围
We've been increasing our radius mile by mile,
在镇周围拓展出半圆形安全区
spreading in a semicircle around the town.
目前已经拓展到了53英里
We've made it 53 miles out so far.
下车后 我们会分成两队
We break into two groups when we step outside our vehicle.
如果有情况 就发射闪光弹
If shit hits, we fire a flare.
两队互相支援
One group gets the other.
这方法不错
Good system.
没错
It is.
另外 你们能来到这里
Still, you're standing here
是因为我们上个月失去了四个人
because we lost four people last month.
发生了什么
What happened?
我们在找补给时碰上了行尸
We were on a run, roamers came out,
那四个人没有守规矩
they didn't follow the system.
他们都是好人
They were good people.
是的
They were.
只是太害怕了
They were just scared.
听着 我会很严厉
Look, I can be a hard-ass.
我知道我很讨人厌
And I know I'm a douchebag.
总得有人领导团队
Someone's got to call the ball around here
而那个人就是我
and that someone is me.
如果你是团队一员 就得无条件服从我
If you're on this crew, you do exactly as I say.
很遗憾你的人遭遇不幸
Sorry you lost your people.
是啊 我们报复过了
Yeah. We got ours.
抓住了一个害死我们人的行尸
Managed to snag one of the deadheads that took them down.
把它吊在那里
Strung it up there.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
现在我们有个热身仪式
Now we have a little pregame ritual.
让我们头脑清醒点
Get our heads on straight.
提醒我们敌人是谁
Remind us what we're up against.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
帮我找到它
Help me find it.
瞧瞧这烂摊子
Look at this shit.
还在滴血 它就在附近
Blood's still wet. It's nearby.
它已经走了
It's gone.
它害死了我们的一个朋友
It took down one of our friends.
它就在附近 我们不会让它跑的
It's nearby, we're not letting it go.
这里 过来 过来
Hey, over here. Come on. Come on.
快来 来我这
Hey, come on. Come at me.
- 不 别碰它 - 你们都退后
- No, don't touch it. - The rest of you, back off.
过来 快啊 过来
Come on. Come on. Come here.
快快 快过来 过来
Come on. Come on. Come on now. Come on!
抓住了
Get him.
该死
Damn it!
不 抓好了
No, hold on to it!
- 搞什么 - 对啊 搞什么
- What the hell?! - Yeah, what the hell?
- 你差点害死她 - 我让你们退后
- You almost got her killed! - I told you all to stay back!
我让你们无条件服从我
I told you to listen to every damn thing I said.
我跟你们说过的
I told you that.
你们三个换工作吧
You three need new gigs.
你们还不适合出去
You're not ready for runs yet.
你恐怕说反了吧
Yeah, pretty sure you got that backwards.
听着 我们有自己的规矩
Look, we got a way of doing things around here.
- 你绑了只行尸 - 它杀了我们的朋友
- You tied up walkers. - It killed our friend.
我不想再纠缠了
Look, I'm not having this conversation.
你们在外面要听我的命令
You obey my orders out there.
那我们就和上一队人一样死定了
Then we're just as screwed as your last run crew.
再说一次
Say that again.
退后 艾登
No, back off, Aiden.
- 来呀 - 拜托老兄 别惹事
- Come on. - Come on, man. Just take a step back.
来呀 硬汉
Come on, tough guy.
没人怕你 老兄
No one's impressed, man.
走开吧
Walk away.
艾登 怎么回事
Aiden! What is going on?
这家伙质疑我们的规矩
This guy's got a problem with the way we do things.
你为什么放他们进来
Why did you let these people in?
因为我们真正知道在外面该怎么做
Because we actually know what we're doing out there.
艾登 不 够了
Aiden, no! That's enough!
我说够了
I said that is enough!
- 别这样 - 他自找的
- Let's not do this now. - Tell him.
你想再被打翻吗
You want to end up on your ass again?
冷静 好吗 达里尔
Cool, all right? Daryl.
所有人听好了
I want everyone to hear me, okay?
瑞克和他的人现在是社区的成员
Rick and his people are part of this community now
享受平等待遇
in all ways as equals.
明白吗
Understood?
明白
Understood.
你们全部上交武器
All of you, turn in your weapons.
你们俩来跟我谈谈
Then you two come talk to me.
我说过会给你安排工作
I told you I had a job for you.
我想任命你为治安官
I'd like you to be our constable.
你以前是警察
That's what you were.
一直都是警察
That's what you are.
你也是
And you, too.
你们接受吗
Will you accept?
好吧
Okay.
好 我接受
Yeah, I'm in.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢什么
For what?
把他打翻
For knocking him on his ass.
你不喜欢我 对吗
You don't like me, do you?
你们应该关上门
You should keep your gates closed.
为什么
Why?
因为现在生存是最重要的
Because it's all about survival now.
不择手段
At any cost.
外面的人虎视眈眈
People out there are always looking for an angle.
伺机利用你的弱点
Looking to play on your weakness.
他们只在乎
They measure you
你有什么价值
by what they can take from you,
怎么利用你生存
by how they can use you to live.
安全吗
We good?
是的
Yeah.
你又当警察了
You a cop again?
我试试大小
I'm trying it on for size.
这么说我们要久留了
So we're staying?
我觉得我们可以分屋睡了
I think we can start sleeping in our own homes.
安顿下来
Settle in.
如果我们太过舒适 会放松戒备
If we get comfortable here, we let our guard down...
这地方会让我们变弱
this place is gonna make us weak.
卡尔也说过这话
Carl said that.
但是不会那样的
But it's not gonna happen.
我们不会变弱
We won't get weak.
我们的骨子里已经没有脆弱
That's not in us anymore.
我们能做到的
We'll make it work.
如果他们做不到
And if they can't make it...
我们就接管这里
then we'll just take this place.